// 15 questions as object arrays
var quiz = [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: 'Which of the following is not a Javascript Primitive?',
        choice: ['String', 'Number', 'Variable', 'Bigint'],
        answer: 'Variable',
        state: true
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: 'Select the Boolean?',
        choice: ['null', 'false', '0', 'undefined'],
        answer: 'false',
        state: true
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: 'Which of the following is a Modulus',
        choice: ['**', '%', '++', '!'],
        answer: '%',
        state: true
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: 'Which of these is an anonymous function?',
        choice: ['function ()', '!function', 'f()', 'function x'],
        answer: 'function ()',
        state: true
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: 'What is Control Flow in a computer?',
        choice: ['The power usage.', 'The order in which it executes code.', 'The speed it executes code.', 'The ability to shutdown.'],
        answer: 'The order in which it executes code.',
        state: true
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: 'Where do you find the <title> element on a HTML page?',
        choice: ['<style>', '<body>', '<base>', '<head>'],
        answer: '<head>',
        state: true
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: 'What is the first index value of an array?',
        choice: ['1', '255', 'i', '0'],
        answer: '0',
        state: true
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: 'Which is used to declare an HTML5 document type ?',
        choice: ['<html>', '<!DOCTYPE html>', '<?php>', '<html5>'],
        answer: '<!DOCTYPE html>',
        state: true
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: 'Which is not a Variable?',
        choice: ['let', 'var', 'const', 'math'],
        answer: 'math',
        state: true
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: "In GitHub, what does 'git pull origin main' do?",
        choice: ['Creates a new branch.', 'Changes to main branch', 'Pulls down the latest main branch.', 'Clones the main branch'],
        answer: 'Pulls down the latest main branch.',
        state: true
    },
    {
        id: 11,
        question: 'Which is not a means to style with CSS?',
        choice: ['external style sheet', 'online', 'internal style sheet', 'inline'],
        answer: 'online',
        state: true
    },
    {
        id: 12,
        question: 'Is Bootstrap a ...?',
        choice: ['Security protocol', 'Javscript language', 'CSS Framework', 'Browser'],
        answer: 'CSS Framework',
        state: true
    },
    {
        id: 13,
        question: 'What does NaN mean?',
        choice: ['Not a number', 'Not always needed', 'Not a negative', 'Not a node'],
        answer: 'Not a number',
        state: true
    },
    {
        id: 14,
        question: 'Which is the strict equality operator?',
        choice: ['=', '==', '!=', '==='],
        answer: 'New York',
        state: true
    },
    {
        id: 15,
        question: 'Which is not a Javascript loop?',
        choice: ['While', 'For', 'If', 'Do...while'],
        answer: 'If',
        state: true
    }  
];
